const quiz = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What data structure processes elements adhering to the FIFO principle?",
    answer: "Queue"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "The space between two adjacent grid lines (row or column) is called grid ...",
    answer: "Track"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the term for a JavaScript function that is passed as an argument to another function?",
    answer: "Callback"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What term is used to describe a technique in CSS where a background image moves at a different speed than the foreground content during scrolling?",
    answer: "Parallax"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What is the term for a combination of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript that is packaged for easy distribution and reuse?",
    answer: "Widget"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What HTML5 element is used to draw graphics, animations, and other visual elements on a webpage?",
    answer: "Canvas"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What tool is commonly used in software development to analyze code for potential errors, style violations, and other issues to ensure code quality and consistency?",
    answer: "Linter"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the JavaScript function that is automatically invoked when an object is created using the \"new\" keyword?",
    answer: "Constructor"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What is the JavaScript feature that allows a function to remember the variables in its lexical scope even if the function is executed outside that scope?",
    answer: "Closure"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What CSS layout model is designed to provide a more efficient and predictable way to arrange and align items within a container, offering a one-dimensional layout approach for improved responsiveness and flexibility?",
    answer: "Flexbox"
  },
];

export default quiz;